{
  "1": {
    "question": " In case, https://abc.com/qxf2/qxf2-page-object-model/actions?query=workflow%3A%22Mark+stale+issues+and+pull+requests%22? gives me access to action workflow-'Mark Stale issues and pull' then how I will access wokflow- Build Redme and deploy dataset for test user and test repository\n(a)https://abc.com/test/test/actions?query=workflow%3A%22Mark+stale+issues+and+pull+requests%22?\n(b)https://abc.com/test/test/actions?query=workflow%3A%22Build+Redme+and+deploy+dataset%22?\n(c)https://abc.com/qxf2/qxf2-page-object-model/actions?query=workflow%3A%22Build+Redme+and+deploy+dataset%22?\n(d)https://abc.com/qxf2/test/actions?query=workflow%3A%22Build+Redme+and+deploy+dataset%22?\n",
    "answer": "b",
    "more_info": "observe  URL's carefully ",
    "user_response": "None"
  },
  "2": {
    "question": "https://abc.com/cost-management/home#/savings-plans/recommendations?spType=COMPUTE_SP&lookbackPeriodInDays=THIRTY_DAYS&termInYears=ONE_YEAR&paymentOption=ALL_UPFRONT&sortKey=instanceFamily&sortOrder=Asc&filter=%5B%5D&scope=LINKED?- When I hit this URL this gives me access to my saving plans where current saving plan is Compute, based on past 30 days for plan term of 1 year and I make all payment upfront now I want to quickly search my another 3-year saving plan for EC2 Instance, where payment option is no upfront and which is calculated based on past 7 days.\n(a)https://abc.com/cost-management/home#/savings-plans/recommendations?spType=EC2_INSTANCE_SP&lookbackPeriodInDays=7_DAYS&termInYears=3_YEAR&paymentOption=NO_UPFRONT&sortKey=instanceFamily&sortOrder=Asc&filter=%5B%5D&scope=LINKED?\n(b)https://abc.com/cost-management/home#/savings-plans/recommendations?spType=EC2_INSTANCE_SP&lookbackPeriodInDays=SEVEN_DAYS&termInYears=3_YEAR&paymentOption=NO_UPFRONT&sortKey=instanceFamily&sortOrder=Asc&filter=%5B%5D&scope=LINKED?\n(c)https://abc.com/cost-management/home#/savings-plans/recommendations?spType=EC2_INSTANCE_SP&lookbackPeriodInDays=7_DAYS&termInYears=THREE_YEAR&paymentOption=NO_UPFRONT&sortKey=instanceFamily&sortOrder=Asc&filter=%5B%5D&scope=LINKED?\n(d)https://abc.com/cost-management/home#/savings-plans/recommendations?spType=EC2_INSTANCE_SP&lookbackPeriodInDays=SEVEN_DAYS&termInYears=THREE_YEAR&paymentOption=NO_UPFRONT&sortKey=instanceFamily&sortOrder=Asc&filter=%5B%5D&scope=LINKED?\n",
    "answer": "d",
    "more_info": "observe  URL's carefully",
    "user_response": "None"
  },
  "3": {
    "question": "https://abc.com/cost-management/home?#/savings-plans/overview? This gives access overview of saving plans, now how should I access overview of Utilisation report then how should I access it\n(a)https://abc.com/cost-management/home?#/utilisation-report/overview?\n(b)https://abc.com/cost-management/home?#/overview/utilisation-report?\n(c)https://abc.com/cost-management/savings-plans?#/home/overview?\n(d)https://abc.com/cost-management/savings-plans?#/overview/home?\n",
    "answer": "a",
    "more_info": "observe  URL's carefully",
    "user_response": "None"
  },
  "4": {
    "question": "https://www.abc.com/search?q=brownie+recipe+-milk gives brownie recipe without milk, if I want to find cake receipe without milk and eggs how should I search it\n(a)https://www.abc.com/search?q=brownie+recipe+-milk+-eggs\n(b)None of the above\n(c)https://www.abc.com/search?q=cake+recipe+-milk+-eggs\n(d)Both of the above\n",
    "answer": "c",
    "more_info": "observe  URL's carefully",
    "user_response": "None"
  },
  "5": {
    "question": "If https://www.abc.com/search?q=info%3Anytimes.com&oq=info%3Anytimes.com gives me serach results associated with New Yoork times.com, which of the following will give me an option to get serach results for Washington Post.com \n(a)https://www.abc.com/search?q=info%3Awashington+post.com&oq=info%3Awashington+post.com\n(b)https://www.abc.com/search?q=info%3Awashingtonpost.com&oq=info%3Awashingtonpost.com\n(c)Both of the above\n(d)None of the above\n",
    "answer": "c",
    "more_info": "observe  URL's carefully",
    "user_response": "None"
  },
  "6": {
    "question": "If https://mail.abc.com/mail/u/0/?tab=rm&ogbl#inbox gives me access to my emails in the inbox then which of the following gives me access to the sent items-\n(a)https://mail.abc.com/mail/u/0/?tab=rm&dgbl#sent\n(b)https://mail.abc.com/mail/u/0/?tab?=rm&ogbl#sent\n(c)https://mail.abc.com/mail/u/0/tab?=rm&ogbl#sent\n(d)either a or b\n",
    "answer": "b",
    "more_info": "observe  URL's carefully",
    "user_response": "None"
  },
  "8": {
    "question": "If https://abc.com/search?q=dynamic+table+with+python gives me serach results for dynamic table with python, now I want to serach can't conctat string to byte then which is the correct search string from below-\n(a)https://abc.com/search?q=can't+concat+string+to+byte\n(b)https://abc.com/search?q=can%27t%20concat%20string%20to%20byte\n(c)Either a or b as both will give same results\n(d)None of the above\n",
    "answer": "b",
    "more_info": "observe  URL's carefully",
    "user_response": "None"
  },
  "9": {
    "question": "if https://ap16.classic.com/home/home.jsp?source=classic gives me access to the classic mode of application how I will access lightening mode of the application \n(a)https://ap16.lightning.com/home/home.jsp?source=lightning \n(b)https://ap16.classic.com/home/homehome.jsp?source=lightening (c)https://ap16.lightening.com/home/homehome.jsp?source=classic\n(d)None of the above\n",
    "answer": "a",
    "more_info": "observe  URL's carefully",
    "user_response": "None"
  },
  "10": {
    "question": "I am accessing test environment using https://my-domain/cit-c/webseal.troy.com where cit is component integration,sit is system intgration, oat operation acceptance testing , c is environment used by testing team,d is dev environment, e is uat environment, troy is an application name. Now I want to access athens application on dev environment used for system intgration then how should I access it \n(a)https://my-domain/cit-d/webseal.athens.com \n(b)https://my-domain/sit-d/webseal.troy.com\n(c)https://my-domain/sit-d/webseal.athens.com\n(d)https://my-domain/sit-c/webseal.athens.com\n",
    "answer": "c",
    "more_info": "observe  URL's carefully",
    "user_response": "None"
  },
  "11": {
    "question": "I am on board card- https://board.com/board/22-jun-2020/287-cassiopeia-22-june-2020? which was created on 22-june-2020, I have created new board card with the name 288-hackthon-15-july-2020, on 15-july-2020 which of the following is correct url to access the card\n(a)https://board.com/b/15-july-2020/288-hackthon-15-july-2020\n(b)https://board.com/board/15-july-2020/288-hackthon-15-july-2020\n(c)https://board.com/board/22-jun-2020/288-hackthon-15-july-2020\n(d)https://board.com/22-jun-2020/288-hackthon-15-july-2020\n",
    "answer": "b",
    "more_info": "observe  URL's carefully",
    "user_response": "None"
  }
}